<html>
	<head><center><h1>ANIME RECOMMENDATION</center></h1>
	<title>Anime Recommendation</title>
	</head>
	<body background="anime2.jpg" text="white"><font face="comic sans ms" SIZE="16"><center>BY: AC METILA AND MARIELLA MONACILLO</FONT><BR>	
	<font face="cooper black"><ol>
	<li>Special A</font><br>
	<p>Special A, also known as Special A or S.A, is a shōjo manga by Maki Minami. The series started serialization in the bimonthly magazine The Hana to Yume in 2003, and moved to the biweekly magazine Hana to Yume in 2004, after running for four chapters.The series ended after 99 chapters on March 19, 2009.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	The story revolves around Hikari Hanazono and Kei Takishima, as well as their Special A Posterfriends and fellow members of S·A. Hikari Hanazono has always been second to Kei Takishima. When they were six years old, their pro-wrestling loving fathers introduced them to each other. Assuming that she was the best in wrestling, young Hikari challenged Kei to a wrestling match only to be thoroughly defeated by him. Ever since that fateful incident, Hikari swore to beat Kei in school grades, sporting events or any competition. To do this, she has enrolled in the same school as Kei since elementary. Now she attends Hakusenkan, an ultra elite school, that costs her carpenter father a lot of money. Hikari and Kei are the top two students in the school, with Kei holding firmly to that number one position. While Hikari considers Kei to be a rival and important friend, she is completely unaware that Kei is in love with her. The story primarily focuses on Hikari and her constant attempts to defeat her one and only rival, Kei, and how she finds love in their rivalry.</p>
	<img src="sa.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Maid Sama</font><br>
	<p>Maid Sama is a shōjo manga series by Hiro Fujiwara. It was serialized in Hakusensha's monthly shōjo manga magazine, LaLa. There are 18 published volumes under the Hana to Yume Comics imprint in Japan.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Once an all-boys school, Seika High, a renowned school full of reckless and filthy students, has recently become a co-ed school. However, with the female population still remaining a minority even after the change over the recent years, Misaki Ayuzawa takes it into her own hands to reform the school and allow a chance for the girls to feel safer in the rough environment. Even the teachers are on her side. Training, studying and even becoming the first female student council president of the school, Misaki has gained a reputation, among the male students body as an uptight boy-hating demon dictator and as a shining hope for the teachers and fellow female students. However, despite her tough-as-nails appearance, she secretly works part-time at a maid café in order to support her family. Unfortunately, her secret is soon discovered by Takumi Usui, a popular boy at Seika High</p>
	<img src="ms.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Code Geass</font><br>
	<p>Code Geass often referred to as simply Code Geass, is a Japanese anime series created by Sunrise, directed by Gorō Taniguchi, and written by Ichirō Ōkouchi, with original character designs by manga authors Clamp. <br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	The story begins with Lelouch and Nunnally being sent as political pawns to Japan to lull the Japanese government into a false sense of security. After the siblings are sent to Japan, Japan is attacked and defeated by Britannia. With the ruins of Japan as a background, Lelouch vows to his Japanese friend Suzaku Kururugi that he will one day obliterate Britannia as an act of vengeance against his father.Seven years later, Lelouch (now going by the name Lelouch Lamperouge), is now a popular yet withdrawn student at Ashford Academy. Lelouch becomes involved in a terrorist attack and finds a mysterious girl called C.C. (C2), who saves Lelouch's life from the Britannian Royal Guard, by making a contract with him and granting Lelouch a power known as Geass (ギアス Giasu). This power, also known as the "Power of Kings" (王の力 Ō no Chikara), allows him to command anyone to do whatever he wants, including bending their will to live, fight, or die on his behalf. This power can affect an individual just once and only through direct eye contact. Lelouch decides to use his Geass to find his mother's murderers, destroy the Britannian Empire, and create a better world where Nunnally can live happily. In the process, Lelouch becomes Zero, a masked vigilante and the leader of the resistance movement known as The Black Knights, gaining popularity and support among the Japanese on his way towards the rebellion of Britannia. However, this does not come without a cost. Caught up in a conflict where he does not know the full extent of his powers, Lelouch will have to battle Suzaku, a resistance member named Kallen Stadtfeld, the strongest army in the world, his own half-siblings, and many others in a battle that will forever change the world.</p>
	<img src="cg.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li></br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Charlotte</font><br>
	<p>Charlotte is a 2015 Japanese anime television series produced by P.A.Works and Aniplex and directed by Yoshiyuki Asai. The anime aired 13 episodes in Japan between July 5 and September 27, 2015.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Plot
	Charlotte follows the story of four students in an alternate reality from Hoshinoumi Academy, a school founded to protect children with special abilities that develop during puberty, as they search for and protect others like them throughout Japan.These students include Yū Otosaka, a boy with the power to control another person, albeit only for 5 seconds and only when directly looking at the target, Nao Tomori, who uses her power to become invisible to one person she chooses in order to convince others to listen to her, Jōjirō Takajō, with the power to move extremely quickly making it look like teleportation, and Yusa Nishimori who is usually possessed by her deceased pyrokinetic sister, Misa, due to her ability as a medium.</p>
	<img src="charlotte.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Ao Haru Ride</font><br>
	<p>Ao Haru Ride is a Japanese shōjo manga series written and illustrated by Io Sakisaka. It began serialization in the February 2011 issue of Shueisha's Bessatsu Margaret and ended in February 2015.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Futaba Yoshioka has a few reasons why she wants to "reset" her image and life as a new high school student. Because she's cute, she was ostracized by her female friends in junior high, and because of a misunderstanding, she couldn't get her feeling across to the only boy she has ever liked, Tanaka-kun.Now in high school, she is determined to be as unladylike as possible so that her friends won't be jealous of her. While living her life this way contentedly, she meets Tanaka-kun again, but he now goes under the name of Kou Mabuchi. He tells her that he felt the same way as she did when they were younger, but now that is the thing of the past. Will Futaba be able to continue her love that never even started from three years ago?</p>
	<img src="ao.jpg" height="150" width="150"></li><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Detective Conan</font><br><br>
	<p>Detective Conan is an ongoing Japanese detective manga series written and illustrated by Gosho Aoyama.It was serialized in Shogakukan's Weekly Shōnen Sunday on January 19, 1994, and has been collected into 94 tankōbon volumes as of December 18, 2017.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Shinichi Kudo, a seventeen year old master detective, had it all. He could solve any case brought to his attention and in record time. His girlfriend, Ran, is a karate expert, and her father is a bumbling P.I. who is driven crazy by the fact that Shinichi gets all of the great cases. One day, while Shinichi and Ran are at an amusement park, the pair become separated. Shinichi catches wind of a dirty deal going down, and spies on a pair of men in dark trenchcoats. He's caught and the men use an experimental poison on him, intending to kill him. However, things don't work exactly as planned. When Shinichi comes to, he finds he's shrunken down to the size of a fourth grader. He goes to the goofball inventor that lives next door to him for help, and the inventor agrees to give him a hand. When Ran comes looking for Shinichi, he and the inventor come up with a story saying that Shinichi is a child named Conan Edogawa (Conan as in Sir Arthur Conan Doyle). Ran offers to let "Conan" live with her family while his "family" is away. Shinichi then makes it his mission to one day find the men who poisoned him and get the antidote. Thus concludes the backstory to the series. In each episode, Conan solves a different case in the style of all good detective shows, giving hints to help the viewer try to guess who the villain is, while trying to keep his true identity a secret.</p>
	<img src="dc.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>One Piece</font><br>
	<p>One Piece is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Eiichiro Oda.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	There once lived a pirate named Gol D. Roger. He obtained wealth, fame, and power to earn the title of Pirate King. When he was captured and about to be executed, he revealed that his treasure called One Piece was hidden somewhere at the Grand Line.The story follows the adventures of Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit. With his crew of pirates, named the Straw Hat Pirates, Luffy explores the Grand Line in search of the world's ultimate treasure known as "One Piece" in order to become the next Pirate King.</p>
	<img src="op.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Fairy Tail</font><br>
	<p>Fairy Tail is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Hiro Mashima.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	The story follows the adventures of Natsu Dragneel, a wizard who is a member of the popular wizards' guild Fairy Tail, as he searches for the dragon Igneel. Lucy, a 17 year old girl, sets out on journey to become a full-fledged wizard and joins the strongest and most (in) famous guild FAIRY TAIL where she meets Natsu, Happy, Gray and Erza, who treat her more like family than friends. This epic series takes us through all the dangers that the members of fairy tail face and eventually overcome through mutual love and friendship.</p>
	<img src="ft.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Magic Kaito</font><br>
	<p>Magic Kaito is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Gosho Aoyama, that began in Shogakukan's Weekly Shōnen Sunday in 1987.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Kaito Kuroba is a normal teenage student whose father died under mysterious circumstances eight years ago. Eight years later, he is made aware of his father's secret identity; a famous international criminal known as Kaito Kid, and that he was murdered by a mysterious organization because he tried to steal a gem which was also targeted by them. The goal of the organization is to find within a year the Pandora Gem, a mystical stone said to shed tears during the passing of the Volley comet (which happens once every 10,000 years): drinking these tears bestows immortality</p>
	<img src="mk.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>
	<font face="cooper black">
	<li>Doraemon</font><br>
	<p>Doraemon It was serialized in Shogakukan's Weekly Shōnen Sunday on January 19, 1994, and has been collected into 94 tankōbon volumes as of December 18, 2017.<br>
	<b>Plot:</b>
	Nobita Nobi is a young boy who suffers from poor grades, frequent bullying and negative emotions like sadness and jealousy. Many years in the future, one of his descendants sends the robotic cat Doraemon back in time to protect and guide Nobita. Doraemon has a four-dimensional pocket from which he produces items known as gadgets, which range from toys and medicine, to technology from the future. Examples include the Bamboo-Copter (Japanese: Take-Koputa), a small piece of headgear that allows flight and the Anywhere Door (Japanese: Doko Demo Doa), a door that opens up to any place the user wishes.Nobita's closest friend is Shizuka Minamoto, who also serves as his romantic interest and eventually becomes his wife. Nobita is usually tormented by the bullying Takeshi Goda (nicknamed "Gian"), and the cunning and arrogant Suneo Honekawa. A typical story consists of Doraemon using one of his gadgets in order to assist Nobita in various ways, often causing more trouble than he was trying to solve.</p>
	<img src="doraemon.jpeg" height="150" width="150"></li><br><br>

	</ol>
	
	&nbsp; &nbsp;<a href="file:///D:/Student/Documents/monacillo%20&%20metila/2.html">About</a>
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; 
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; 		&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;
	<a href="file:///D:/Student/Documents/monacillo%20&%20metila/11.html">Manga</a>
	</body></center>
</html>